If I'm out in society, and I'm supposed
to make a decision, but I'm not ready to
make one, I can just look at that person
and go, "Excuse me,
I have to check with my wife."
>> [laughter]
>> And then they have to look back at me
and go, "But of course.
Uh so far it's been going well, man. I
flew in today. My plane landed. We love
that.
Yeah, got to celebrate the landings.
Yeah.
I feel like we got to start doing that,
especially this year. You know?
I know we were all rolling our eyes at
the people that clap when we land. Not
this year, man.
Cuz we were getting a little cocky,
weren't we?
Just assuming that they all would land.
And then this year a bunch of them were
like, "No."
>> [laughter]
>> And we had the nerve to be surprised. I
knew we were getting too cocky when we
started introducing budget airlines into
the mix. That
That shouldn't be a thing.
>> [laughter]
>> There shouldn't be budget flying. We
should all fear flying and want to pay
as much as possible for it.
We should be going to the airline like,
"How much do you need
to make sure this goes smoothly?"
>> [laughter]
>> But collectively, a bunch of us just
started going, "Yeah, no. Give me the
airline that cuts every corner."
>> [laughter]
>> Just fill that thing up with 87 regular.
>> What's that? It's a refurbished Boeing?
Wow. Sounds like savings for me.
I love my wife. I even love the word
wife. It's got such power to it. Wife,
you know? If I'm out in society, and I'm
supposed to make a decision, but I'm not
ready to make one, I can just look at
that person and go, "Excuse me,
I have to check with my wife."
>> [laughter]
>> And then they have to look back at me
and go, "But of course.
>> [laughter]
>> I can't expect a decision from you at
this time.
>> [laughter]
>> Well, you must check with YOUR WIFE.
OH, BEAUTIFUL. Doesn't matter how big
the the question is. It could be a
life-changing job opportunity. It could
be something as small as the right slice
of pizza.
I have to check with my wife, and then I
can leave, and then I can come back, and
I can cut to the front of the line. I
have now checked with my wife.
And it'll be pepperoni.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, beautiful. Wife, man. Ladies have
it, too. Husband Husband has that power,
right? Someone knocks on your door,
they're trying to switch out your
shingles. I have to check with my
husband.
But, of course. Although
husband's a little different. Doesn't
have the same power in certain places
you go. Like the more progressive the
environment, the less power husband has.
Like if you're in a really nice coffee
shop in a city
and you say, "I have to check with my
husband." They're looking back at you
like,
"So, that's what we marched for?"
>> [laughter]
>> "Are you chained to his radiator?"
>> But, you can still reclaim that power of
husband. You just have to tweak it
slightly in those environments. If
you're in that environment at that
coffee shop, "I have to check with my
husband." No, you don't say it like
that. You look at them and go, "I have
to check with my pregnant husband."
Now you're back on top.
And but, of course.
Good to go.
We've been together for 14 years now,
and what my favorite part about being
together this long is seeing other
couples in different stages, but
especially when you get to go out
together, and you see another couple
also out not having a good time.
You usually hear it at dinner a few
tables over. You can't make out the
words, but you can catch the vibe. It's
a lot of like,
>> [clears throat]
[snorts]
[laughter]
>> And I just nudge my wife like
Not us tonight.
Oh, I love it, man. It's beautiful, man.
Especially the younger they are. Like
you ever see a 19-year-old couple
fighting in the streets?
Mwah, that is
>> [laughter]
>> When I see that, I'm like, "Babe, forget
what we had planned. I want to watch
this."
>> [laughter]
>> So sloppy. Just all the emotions out
there for everyone to watch.
Usually the girl is running out first,
just straight into the street. She's
holding herself. "Wow, you're there and
you weren't even like looking for me."
And I'm like, "Where are you?" She's
always cold.
>> [laughter]
>> It could be August, she's freezing.
Like, "Where are you?" And he's coming
out after, has no idea what's going on.
He's coming after, just full tilt, just
"Are you serious right now?
Are you serious right now?" He can never
fathom that she is in fact serious in
this moment.
He thinks he's going to go, "Are you
serious?" And she's going to look back,
"No.
>> [laughter]
>> I got you."
But then she doubles down cuz he's not
taking her serious, and then he really
puts his foot down, lays it all down. He
goes, "Honestly, babe, bumping for reals
right now?
You're acting crazy."
>> [laughter]
>> Wrong move, buddy. Wrong move.
>> You call a girl crazy, she'll do
everything she can to prove you right.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
AM I DATING GOKU? WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
>> [laughter]
>> It's never worked. And you'll still see
it. Literally, you go to the bar scene
in your city tonight, you'll see a guy
call his girl crazy in public. And when
I see that, I'm like, "Go for it, pal."
>> [laughter]
>> Or maybe you should also say she should
calm down.
>> [laughter]
>> And I love seeing that, cuz
14 years in, you don't fight like that.
No, it's you don't do it in the streets
in a street brawl. No.
We fight now, it's jujitsu.
>> [laughter]
>> Every move has a counter move.
You hear yourself say something at
dinner, and you think to yourself,
"Better have some replies ready for that
one."
>> [laughter]
>> And that one's going to come up.
You're not doing it in the streets.
Also, there's no emotional like output
that just blows out, cuz you'll see
these young couples, and they're they're
looking at each other after in the pit
of the argument, like, "How did we get
here?"
So cute.
Cuz if my wife and I are arguing,
there's no how did we get No, if I track
back in the series of events,
>> [laughter]
>> I can find one spot where I had a
conversation with my ego.
Uh what should we do, man? Should we say
sorry? NO, NOT TONIGHT.
>> [laughter]
>> OKAY, for sure an option, but maybe we
hear her out a little, blend both
realities, come to a solution. No,
TONIGHT WE FIGHT.
>> [laughter]
>> TONIGHT WE WILL BE RIGHT.
I'D RATHER BE RIGHT THAN ALONE.
And then you fight, and then you're
right, and alone.
>> [laughter]
>> I seem to have miscalculated.
I know most of you don't know me, so I'd
like to give you guys just a little beat
just to take in this face. I know it's a
lot.
>> [laughter]
>> Lot of sharp angles coming at you right
now.
I got a face like a Cybertruck.
>> [laughter]
>> You know, sometimes I see it in the
mirror myself and I'm like, "Whoa, they
make them like that?" You know?
I can feel some of you guys are
wondering how I can look like Beavis and
Butthead
>> [laughter]
>> at the same time.
How is it both?
I know. I know when I got this haircut,
I was like, "Oh, we made a decision."
>> [laughter]
>> And I'm rolling with it, you know? Want
to start doing some petty crime around
town.
>> [laughter]
>> Just some gentle thievery.
Just as a prank on your police sketch
artist.
>> [laughter]
>> When he's on his seventh sketch of butt
Beavis.
>> [laughter]
>> This is the guy that stole your burgers?
>> FUNNY GUYS. HAHA.
I'M GOING TO CALL UP HIS OFFICE line to
a long pause and then just
>> [laughter]
>> You'll never get me.
I am Cornholio.
>> [laughter]
[cheering]
>> It's tough to be on the road, tough to
be away from my house plants. They're
doing really good right now.
Yeah, pretty proud of them. We got some
plant parents in the audience tonight?
Well, nice. Hey, we got a few. All
right. I like saying plant parents cuz I
can feel it divide the crowd.
>> [laughter]
>> Between the people who own plants and
the people who own children.
>> [laughter]
>> I know, I say plant parent. I can feel a
couple people
What?
You just [laughter] call himself a
parent for a plant?
Parent for a plant.
I'm sorry, if your plant dies, do the
cops show up?
>> [laughter]
>> Dead and bang, so. Okay, well, I mean,
there are times I've wanted to overwater
my kid, but I didn't do it.
We've never met these parents.
>> [laughter]
>> So, you have these parents, I guess.
But, you do feel proud of your plants
when they progress like a parent would.
Like, I got this baby rubber plant, and
for a whole year, used to sprout out a
leaf and then down. Leaf and then down.
I'll be looking at it and like, "Dude, I
can't take the emotional turmoil.
Either stick around or don't."
>> [laughter]
>> And then this year, buddy girl's 12 in
He's gaining bark action around the
base.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm walking by, I'm like, "Who you
trying to impress?
>> [laughter]
>> Cuz it's working."
Right before I left, man, he he popped
out a new leaf.
Yeah, try and mess with my energy on a
new leaf week.
>> [laughter]
>> Cannot be done.
Cuz you never know how your plants are
doing. Like, they're great listeners,
but they never tell you how they feel.
What do they think about the plants?
But, on a new leaf week, that's like
them looking at you. Hey, bro.
I love it here.
>> [laughter]
>> Well, yo, you do, man.
Someone's gunning for a fertilizer
stick.
>> [laughter]
>> Makes me want to get a kid, you
>> Sometimes I feel confident that I want a
kid, but then I'll ask a parent how it
is and they are the worst at pitching
it.
>> [laughter]
>> Try it. Ask any active parent, "How is
it having kids?" They'll look back at
you like
"Best thing I ever did."
>> [laughter]
>> "OH YEAH?" "YEAH, I CAN'T IMAGINE my
life without them."
>> [laughter]
>> Sound like a hostage.
Sound like your baby's got a knife to
your back.
"Tell them what I told you to say."
>> [laughter]
>> I like being a dude. It's been good
lately.
It's been good for a while, but also
It's fun. It's fun to travel around
because I've noticed dudes have all
melted together recently. I don't know
if you've noticed this, but anywhere you
travel, if you're around a group of
dudes and they get excited, they all say
the same thing.
"Let's go!"
"Let's go!" If you hear that in the
streets and nearby there's another group
of dudes, they're like, "Where are we
going?"
>> [laughter]
>> They form a larger pack.
It's beautiful, man, cuz guys are all
about going, you know, "Let's go! Go
team go!" That song goes hard. "I'm
going in!"
Ladies get excited and it's the exact
opposite. When ladies get excited,
they're like, "Stop."
>> [laughter]
>> "Stop that."
"No, shut up. I can't even."
No wonder we have so much trouble
communicating.
>> [laughter]
>> We have the same emotion, we say the
opposite thing.
"Let's go!" "Stop."
>> [laughter]
>> "What's wrong with them, man?"
That's what it is. Guys are go, girls
are stop. Non-binary,
"Yield."
>> [applause]
>> Are you stop or you go?
>> Depends on the situation.
>> [laughter]
>> This is great. I I am looking forward to
going to sleep after this. This is going
to be good.
>> [laughter]
>> I mean, don't get me wrong. This is
great. I'm going to enjoy all this, but
sleep's the best. I love sleep, man. I
like waking up, too.
Cuz when you wake up, that's when you
get to remember sleep.
>> [laughter]
>> And those good stuff we just did.
Sometimes waking up so good
you go back to sleep.
We're getting a twofer on today.
That's when you have those good dreams.
That's when your dream brain cooks.
Those little cat naps in the morning,
you come out of those and you remember
you're like you're in shop class in high
school and your teacher was there upset
so you ate a wrench and your dad was
there and he was mad cuz you're bad at
yoga.
>> [laughter]
>> Logical brain hasn't woken up yet, so
physically you're just like was that a
cinematic masterpiece?
>> [laughter]
>> I think it was.
I should tell everyone.
>> [laughter]
>> Don't give into this. Never give into
this. Never tell anyone about the dream
that you had. Having a great dream is
like having a great poop. It's just for
you.
>> [laughter]
>> Be proud you had it and take it to the
grave.
>> [laughter]
>> It's weird. It's weird how the older you
get, the more you love sleep, you know?
When you're young, you hate it. When
you're 7 years old, if you hear the word
bedtime, you're like, "That's
triggering."
It's the worst. I can remember my
parents forcing that on me in the middle
of the day.
>> Yeah, you're cranky.
You go take a nap.
>> And I can remember looking back at them
with the devil in my eyes like, "I'm not
even tired."
>> [laughter]
>> Could you imagine if in the middle of
your day today
somebody forced you to take a nap?
Was this a spa day?
>> [laughter]
>> You can twist my arm. Oh, no.
Are we Spanish? I think we're Spanish.
Sometimes I don't like waking up though.
Sometimes I don't.
And it's not a sad thing. It's just I
hate waking up to alarms, you know? I
hate beeps. Hate waking up to alarms.
Especially my wife's wake up alarm. I
feel like there are two kinds of people
when it comes to alarms in this world.
You have people like me who like to wake
up to just a soft, gentle
almost inaudible like a do do do do do
do.
>> [laughter]
>> So soft it can enter dream world.
>> You're bouncing around in dream world.
All of a sudden you hear do do do do do
do. Where is that familiar sound?
Maybe I should move towards that
and seamlessly start the next day.
>> [laughter]
>> And then you got the second kind of
person like my wife who likes to wake up
to a nuclear evacuation.
>> [laughter]
>> iPhone at a volume level I didn't know
it was capable of.
Just oh, full Chernobyl. That's how
we're STARTING THE DAY?
>> [laughter]
>> AND YOU KNOW THE INTERESTING THING ABOUT
THIS KIND OF PERSON?
They don't even wake up.
>> [laughter]
>> No, no. Chime guy gets jolted into
existence.
What's happening?
He has to hurt locker his way over to
her phone.
>> [laughter]
>> Diffuse the situation.
Why are we turning that into a bit of a
saga?
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, but that was only 7:57.
>> We still got 8:01 coming down the
pipeline.
16 more alarms spread out sporadically.
How is your ideal wake up between 8:00
a.m. and 11:30?
And why does 8:07 have two?
>> [laughter]
>> I never understand.
That's honestly like the only thing that
my wife consistently does that bothers
me and there are a lot of things I do
that bother her.
Working on it.
We were talking about it the other day.
We're working on nose-blowing technique
in public.
Thought I had that one down. I did.
Turns out no.
>> [laughter]
>> You never know. You never know when
there's a skill that just needs to be
worked on. It's coming at you, man.
The other day, messed [snorts] up real
bad, man. I uh
>> [sighs]
>> dried my feet off with the wrong towel.
>> [laughter]
>> She watched me do it. She asked anyway,
"What did you just do, Jess now?"
I I dried my feet off with a towel.
"What kind of towel is that?"
The closest.
It's the closest towel.
She's very patient with me. So, so
that's a hand towel. Yeah. So, we
wouldn't use a hand towel on the feet.
>> [laughter]
>> In my defense,
the feet are the hands of the legs.
>> [laughter]
>> So, I thought I was justified in doing
that.
Mhm. Mhm. Okay. All right. Thought I had
it down, man. A little while later, I
was in the kitchen. I was cleaning up,
man. We just had that conversation. My
hands, they were covered in a sauce and
a little bit of spice on them. And I was
going over and I was like, "Hands.
Hands."
Hands.
And I went and I grabbed one of the
fluffy hand towels from the bathroom.
>> [laughter]
>> All I heard was, "Absolutely not."
>> You said hand towel for the hands. Hand
hand. I got it right. It's on the chart.
>> [laughter]
>> She goes, "No, it's the kitchen. It's
tea towels only in the kitchen."
I said, "What about the paper towels?"
She goes, "That's not even a towel.
And that's the one you should have
used."
>> [laughter]
>> I'm going to fail this test.
Like, I don't I don't know how all women
just know the towel hierarchy.
>> [laughter]
>> It just comes pre-programmed.
But, you have to understand, for us
dudes, it does not.
Maybe our moms try and teach us. They
try to instill it in us. But, when we
leave home, we have to go off into the
world. We completely forget. Cuz when we
go off into the world, we have to live
with dudes
in dude houses.
And a dude house
is towel anarchy.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't feel like ladies fully
understand that. Do you understand what
a dude house is? Do you understand that
a towel could never hang in a dude house
bathroom?
No. It gets deployed there to serve.
>> [laughter]
>> It's going in for multiple tours.
>> When a dude house towel goes in, oh,
it's soft and innocent. But, when it
comes out, it's hard.
>> [laughter]
>> 6 months went by before I got back to
the wash.
Missing half my body now.
>> [laughter]
>> And then you expect us to adjust when we
live with you in these houses where you
got the big towels and the smaller
towels and even littler towels. Like a
Russian doll set of towels.
>> [laughter]
>> Trying to get it down, man. And I know
some of you, if you've been following my
comedy for a while, you might be looking
at me like, "Andrew, you've talked about
towels before in your last special. Why
are you still talking about them?"
And
it's because my wife and I still are.
>> [laughter]
>> I can't seem to get it down.
Every time I think I'm good, I mess up
again, man.
>> [laughter]
>> I was after a shower. I was just drying
myself off and P after shower, she came
into the bathroom all happy, saw me,
face dropped. She's like, "What are you
doing?" I was like, "Drying myself off."
She goes,
"That's a bath mat."
>> [laughter]
>> It's the same fabric as a towel.
>> Look at the size of it. I thought I got
bigger.
>> [laughter]
>> Now, see guys struggle with this a lot,
this whole idea of being wrong all the
time. You know, you know, I've seen my
buddies break up over it. She just find
a way to convolute the argument so she's
right, I'm wrong every time. And it's
how is that possible? I was like, "No."
And something I've wrestled with, too.
But, I have come to a conclusion that
that is how it should be.
She should be right every time.
And I can feel the guys pulling back on
me right now.
I want to just display I'm not a broken
man up here, okay?
I'm not up here like, "Guys, come on.
Happy wife, happy life."
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> No, there's logic here. This is your
person. This is the person you're adding
to your life. What would you rather?
Some girl who's wrong all the time?
So, what you want as your person? Just
some stupid chick?
Just following you around, "Wow, what
you're wearing is perfect for where
we're going. That's great. Yeah."
>> [laughter]
>> And then that girl I don't know was nice
to you, and then you were nice back.
Yay.
>> [laughter]
>> You can dry your feet off with any towel
you see.
>> [applause]
>> No, I want someone who compliments my
weaknesses, and that's what I've
noticed. I am not emotionally
intelligent. She's way more emotionally
intelligent than I am. And I know this
cuz every time I ask her how she feels,
she knows.
>> [laughter]
>> Immediately. No delay. There's emotion.
>> She asks me how I feel, and there's
always just a long pause.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm buffering.
And then she gets upset like I'm keeping
the information from her.
>> [laughter]
>> She's like, "Just tell me how you feel."
She's like, "Tell me how you feel. Like,
how do you feel?" I'm like, "I too am
asking that question."
>> [laughter]
>> There's just nothing coming back.
But, how do you feel?
I have to check WITH MY WIFE.
IT'S THE ONLY time it doesn't work.
>> [applause]
>> It's been great chatting with you you My
name's Andrew Packer. Have a great
night, guys.
guys. Cheers.